toptechlive.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy - Top Tech Live

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by Contact us Page.

At http://www.toptechlive.com/, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by nhttp://www.toptechlive.com/ and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites,http://www.toptechlive.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies And Web Beacons:

http://www.toptechlive.com/ does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.toptechlive.com/.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.toptechlive.com/ and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
